Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Farnham, Phil, undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - John Farquharson Ltd. Literary Agents, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Fasanella, Ralph, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Ference, Mary Lou, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Ferguson Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Ferrill, Meghan, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Ferriss, Lucy, undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - The Fiction Project, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - The Field Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - The Film Fund, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Film Writers Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - The Finegan Family, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Fine Arts Work Center in Provincetown, undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Finkelstein, Katherine, undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Finkelstein Memorial Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Finland House, undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Fisch, Marilyn, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - The Alexander Fischbein Foundation, undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Fish, Hamilton, undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Fitelson, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Fitzgerald, Ed, undated (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - F. Scott Fitzgerald Literary Conference, undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Florida State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Florida, University of-, undated (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Folger Shakespeare Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - The Folio Society, undated (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Ford, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Ford Times, undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Fordham University, undated (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Forman, Milos, undated (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Fosse, Bob, undated (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Fosburgh, Lacey, undated (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Foster City, City of-, undated (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Foundation for Middle East Peace, undated (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Fowler, Jennifer, undated (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Fraim, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Francke, Linda Bird, undated (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Franklin and Marshall College, undated (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - The Franklin Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Lynn C. Franklin Associates, Ltd., undated (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - The Free Library of Philadelphia, undated (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Freedman, Abby, undated (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - The Freedom Forum, undated (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Freedom from Hunger, undated (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, undated (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Freeze Voter, undated (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Fresh Start, undated (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Fried, Philip, undated (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Friedan, Betty, undated (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Frieden, Miles, undated (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Friedlander, Walter, undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Friedrichs, Kurt, undated (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Friendly Press, undated (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Friends of Libraries, U. S. A., undated (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Friends of Roosevelt Island Landmarks, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Friends in Deed, undated (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Fruchtman, Lisa, undated (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Frumkes, undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Fund for Artists' Colonies, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Fund for Free Expression, undated (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Fund for Free Expression, undated (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Fund for Independent Publishing, undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Fund for New Priorities in America, undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Fund for Open Information and Accountabilit, Inc, undated (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Furman, Roy, undated (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - "Ga-Gh", undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "Gi-Go", undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Gr-Gz", undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gabalova, Zdenka, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gaddis, William, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gale Research Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gannett Suburban Newspapers, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Gannon University, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Garcia, Lisa, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Gardener, Peter, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gardner, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Garfinkel, Patricia, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Garland Publishing, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Gasvoda, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gaven, Marcia Mitzman, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gaven, Tom, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Gelfand, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Gelfman, Schneider Literary Agents, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - General Artists Corporation, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - General Learning Corporation, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Gentlemen's Quarterly, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Geo, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - George Mason University, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Georgetown University, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Georgia, The University of-, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - German Academic Exchange Program (DAAD), undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - German Association for American Studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - German Book Fair, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - German Television (NDR and ARD), undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Gershman, Elizabeth, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Gerstein, Sherry, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Gettysburg Review, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Gibson, Kathryn, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Gibson, Ralph, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Giesa, Alicia, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Gifted Child Society, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Gilbert, Caroline, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Gills, Donald, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - The Allen Ginsberg Memorial Committee, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Gittleson, Celia, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Giuliani, Rudolph, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Givit Haviva Educational Foundation, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Glaser, Edwin, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Glimmer Train Press, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - The Glove Museum, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Glucksman, Louis and Loretta, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Goddard College, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Godfrey, Jim, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - David R. Godine Publisher, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Goethe House, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Goforth, Jon and Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Gold, Herbert, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Goldblum, Tracey, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Goldhurst, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Goldhurst, William, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Emma Goldman Papers (UC - Berkeley), undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Goldsmith, Alice, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Goldsmith, Barbara, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Goldsmith, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Goldwater Hospital, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Goncz, Arpad, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - The Good Book Guide, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Goodheart, Elise, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Goodman, Carolyn, undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Goodman, Mitch, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Goodman, Sol and Edith, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Gordon, Dean, undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Gordon, Eric, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Gordon, J. James, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Gorman, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Gotfryd, Bernard, undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Grabson, Celia, undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Kathini Graham Limited, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Percy Grainger Library Society, undated (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Grand, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Grand Street, undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Granta, undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Gray, Francine and Cleve, undated (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Gray, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - The Great Auk, undated (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Great Valley School District, undated (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Green, Mark, undated (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Green Mountain Post Films, undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Greenberg, Georgia Shreve, undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Greenberg, Marilyn, undated (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Elaine Greene Limited, undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Greenwich High School, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Gregory, Andre, undated (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Grey, Jo and Joel, undated (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Greystone Communications Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Grolier Electronic Publishing, Inc, undated (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni, undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Gross, Harvey, undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Gross, Jerry, undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Grossman, Patty, undated (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Group for the South Fork, undated (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Grove / Atlantic, undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Guild Hall, undated (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Guilford College, undated (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Gulliver, undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Gurganus, Alan, undated (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Gyldendal Publishers, undated (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - "Ha-Hn", undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Ho-Hz", undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Haagse Post Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hadassah, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Haiti Foundation, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Halban, Peter, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Halberg, Marilyn, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Half Shell Productions, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hall, Donald, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hall, Eric, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hall, Oakley, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hamburg, Morton, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Hamilton, Ian, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Hampshire College, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Hampton Click, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hampton Day School, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hampton Library, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hanig, Joshua, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Hansen, Betty, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Harbourfront, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Harking, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - De Harmonie, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Harrington, Michael, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Harbor & Row Publishers, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Harper's Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Harris, Tina, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Harrison Public Library, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - The Hartford Courant, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Harvard University, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Harvard University Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Harvey, Charlotte, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Hastings-on-Hudson Public Library, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Haverford College, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Hawkes, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - The Hay Festival, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Hayden, Brad, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - The Heart Book Group, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Hebrew Arts School, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Hebrew Union College, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Hecht, Paul, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Heepe, Hans George, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Heineman, James, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Heiney, Donald, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Hellemann, Jarl, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Hellman, Lillian, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Helsinki Watch, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Hemingway Days Festival, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Henderson, Pauline, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Henley, Don, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Hepburn, Katherine Houghton, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Herzfeld, Leslie, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Hessisches Literatur Büro, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Heyman, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Highland Park High School, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Lawrence Hill Books, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Himmirsky / Bulgarian Embassy, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Hite, Sid, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Hoagland, Edward, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - John L. Hochman Books, undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Hochman, Sandra, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Hochschild, Adam, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Hochschild, Kay, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Hodder & Stoughton Publishers, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Hoffberg, Oberfest, Berger & Berger, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Abbie Hoffman Defense Fund, undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Hoffman, Andrew, undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Hoffman, Gloria, undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Hofstra University, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Holden, Bill, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Holistic Education Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Hollins College, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Hollywood Policy Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Hollywood Reporter, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Homestead, Magnus, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Honig, Edwin, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Hoopes, Roy, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Hoquet, Aileen, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Horace Greeley High School, undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Glenn Horowitz Bookseller, undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Horwitz, Murray, undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Houghton Mifflin, undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - House & Garden, undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Houston, City of-, undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Howe, Irving, undated (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Howell, Barbara, undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Howell, Douglass Morse, undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - The Huck Group, undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Hudson County Community College, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - The Hudson River Museum, undated (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Hudson Valley Writer's Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Hughes, Lawrence, undated (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Huguenot - Thomas Paine Historical Society, undated (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Human Rights Watch, undated (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Humber School of Creative Writing, undated (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Hunter College, undated (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Huntington Public Library, undated (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Husarka, Anna, undated (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Huttner, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Hyperion, undated (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - "I", undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ibsen Society of America, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Icelandic National Broadcasting Service, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Idaho, University of-, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Illinois Association for Media in Education, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - University of Illinois Press, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Illinois, Urbana-Champaign, University of-, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Illusion Productions, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Immaculate Heart College Center, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Indiana University Writers' Conference, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Indianapolis, University of-, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Indianapolis-Marion County Public Library, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Inostrannaya Literatura, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Instant Classics, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Contemporary Psychotherapy, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Media Analysis, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Human Relations, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Institute of International Education, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - International Association of Crime Writers, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - International Association of Political Consultants, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - International Biographical Centre, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - International Center for Development Policy, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - International Communication Agency, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - International Creative Management, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - International Creative Management, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - International Creative Management, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - International Creative Management, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - International Creative Management, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - International Creative Management, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - International Famous Agency, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - International Furnishings and Design Association, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - International IMPAC Dublin Literary Award, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - International Institute for the Arts, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - International Institute for Secular Humanistic Judaism, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - International Jazz Coalition, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - International Museum of Peace and Solidarity, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - International Poetry Forum, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - International Rescue Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - International Research & Exchange Board, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - International Writers Reunions, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Interreligious Council of New Rochelle, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Interview, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Iona College, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Iowa, University of-, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Ireland, U.S. Embassy of-, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Irish Times, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Irving, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Isaacson, Walter, undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Islands: An International Magazine, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Israel, U.S. Embassy of-, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - "J", undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Jackson, Lee, undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Jacksonville Public Libraries, undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Jaffe, Herb, undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Jaffe, Marc, undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Jagger, Bianca, undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Jagoda, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Jamestown Publishers, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Janeway, Elizabeth, undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Janklow, Morton, undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Janowitz, Tama, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Janus Books, Ltd., undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - John Jay Estate, undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Jazz Section, undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Jeffers, Charles, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Jefferson County Public Schools, undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Jennings, Peter, undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Jeong, Sangjun, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Jerusalem Foundation, undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Jerusalem International Book Fair, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Jewish Community Center of Dallas, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Jewish Community Center of Chicago, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Jewish Community Center of Detroit, undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Jewish Community Center of Greater Rochester, undated (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Jewish Community Center of Southern New Jersey, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Jewish Heritage Book Festival, undated (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Jewish Museum, undated (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Jewish Public Library, undated (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Jews for Radical and Economic Justice, undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Jie, Tao, undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - John Adams Institut, undated (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - John Jay National Scholarship Program, undated (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - John Jermain Memorial Library, undated (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Johns Hopkins University, undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Johnson, Greg, undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Johnston, Albert, undated (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Johnston, Augusta, undated (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Jokerman Publications, undated (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Jonas, Susan, undated (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Jones, Gloria re: James Jones, undated (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Jong, Erica, undated (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Michael Joseph, Ltd., undated (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Joseph the Provider, undated (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Jujamcyn Theaters, undated (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - "Ka-Kh", undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Ki-Kz", undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Kahn, Marcia, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Kalfopoulou, Adrianne, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kanin, Garson, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kansas State University, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Kansas University of-, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Kaplan, Johanna, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Kaplowitz, Irwin, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Karatzaferi, Ioanna, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Kates, Jim, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Katherine Engel Center for Older People, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Katz, Steve, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Katzenberg, Jeffrey, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - [re:] Kaye, Buddy, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Keillor, Garrison, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Kennedy, Bill, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy, Eleanore and Michael, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Kennesaw College, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Kent State University, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Kentucky Book Fair, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Kenyon College, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Kenyon College, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - The Kenyon Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Key Porter Books, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Key West Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Kiefer, Christian, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Kiepenheur & Witsch, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Kimberling, Ronald, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - King, Alan, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - The King's English, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Kingswood-Oxford School, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Kinnell, Galway, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Kinneret Publishing House, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Kirkland, Will, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Kissel, Howard, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Kitman, Marvin, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Klein, Dennis, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - [re:] Kleist, Heinrich von, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Klingerman, Ethel, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Knapp, Peggy, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Knjizevna smotra, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Knutson, Nancy, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Kodansha, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Koeing, Mana, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Koeing, Richard, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Koktejl Magazine, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Kollek, Teddy, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Koning, Hans, undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Kooks, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Korinek, Otakar, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Koster Literary Agency, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Kraft, Joseph, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Kramer, Larry, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Kranich, Michael, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Krementz, Jill, undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Krieger, Murray, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Krupat, Arnold, undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - K & S Associates, undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Kuhn, Jeffrey, undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Kusta, Algis, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - "La-Lh", undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Li-Lz", undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - La Farge, Annik, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - La Trobe University, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Labalme, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lafayette College, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lambo, Selma, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lampert, Zohra, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Landau, Jay, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lande, Nathaniel, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Landers, Jon, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Landsman, Marcia, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Langus, Wally, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Larkin, Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Larson, Marsha, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Lass, Mike, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)